WAI LWIN PHYO

BIM ENGINEER / BIM COORDINATOR



CONTACT

Yangon, Myanmar +95 9420 093 402 wailwinphyo.contact@gmail.com

SKILLS

3D BIM Modeling
Revit Family Creation
3D Coordination and Collaboration
Dynamo Visual Programming

LANGUAGE

English (Fluent)
Burmese (Native)

EDUCATION

Thanlyin Technological University **2013-2019**

BE in Civil Engineering

Zeon Light Training Center **2022**

Automation BIM Essential (Dynamo)

BIM Myanmar Training Center **2021**

3D BIM Coordination

BIM Myanmar Training Center **2020**

Revit Family Creation

PROFILE

Enthusiastic about BIM/VDC technology and BIM automation using visual programming. Professionally experienced Revit user with 4 years of experience involved in the most innovative and exciting infrastructure and building projects around the world. Seeking to advance my career by growing with your company.

EXPERIENCE

RD Studio

Revit Families Modeler (2024 - Present)

- ▶ Create 2D and 3D detailed and complex Revit Families
- ▶ Collaborate with architects to understand their needs and translate them into high-quality BIM models
- Regularly update and refine Revit Families to ensure they meet the evolving needs of architectural projects
- ▶ Participate in the development and implementation of BIM standards and best practices within the company
- ▶ Provide technical support and guidance on Revit modeling to other team members
- ▶ Maintain an up-to-date portfolio of Revit Family models, documenting the process and final outcomes
- Continuously enhance skills and knowledge in Revit Family modeling and stay abreast of industry developments and software updates

KEDMOR Engineers Limited

BIM Engineering Team Leader (2023 - 2024)

- ▶ Overseeing team functionality and ensuring targets are met
- Ensuring continuous workflow for team members
- Monitoring work progress through regular sampling
- ▶ Conducting internal reviews to ensure the quality of deliverables
- Developing a team's work-plan, divided by projects
- ▶ Providing BIM support and training to new team members
- ▶ Coordinating work with other team leaders
- ▶ Ensuring optimal utilization of company resources

BIM Engineer (2022 - 2023)

- ▶ Creation of 3D structural Revit models
- ▶ Undertakes structural coordination for a variety of different

BIM PORTFOLIO

BIM Portfolio



projects, including buildings, bridges and infrastructure, within BIM environment

- ▶ Preparation and production of detailed engineering drawings for all stages of design
- Management and maintenance of the office BIM standards, templates and processes
- ▶ Creation of standardized Revit families for use within the office

BYMA Myanmar Limited Under Bouygues Construction

Design Coordinator (2020 – 2022)

Assistant Drafter (2019 - 2020)

- ▶ Creation of 3D BIM model utilizing Autodesk Revit
- ▶ Manages and updates BIM model as per latest EIFs
- ▶ Coordinates and checks discrepancies across different disciplines
- ▶ Conducts clash detection and prepares RFIs
- ▶ Coordinates and reviews RFI responses into BIM model
- ▶ Produces and issues construction coordinated shop drawings
- ▶ Reviews RFIs issued to date and ensures that all RFIs have been correctly incorporated into latest drawing submissions
- ▶ Creates and modifies Revit families and components necessary for the project
- ▶ Exports required schedules of elements from Revit for further usages
- ▶ Makes records of issued shop drawings and RFIs for later reviews